

DEAN HANS FELANDIO SETIADI SAPUTRA

Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia 082210161832 • hans.dean@yahoo.com linkedin.com/in/hans-felandio

A dedicated computer science student and scholarship student mentor **EXPLORE MY PROJECTS** with a passion for front-end development, and providing solutions for data-related projects and predictive tasks using machine learning and deep learning approaches. Beyond my technical expertise, I have proven to have strong collaboration and creative abilities as an activist of HIMTI BINUS and design & documentation division's co-coordinator.



https://hancreation.github.io/

SKILLS

Front-End Development: React.js, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS.

Data Science & Machine Learning: Python, Data Visualizing, Data Preprocessing, Data Cleaning,

Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Pandas, Matplotlib, Scikit-Learn, PyTorch, Tensorflow.

Programming Language: Python, Java, JavaScript, Typescript, SQL.

Soft Skills: Collaboration, Teamwork, Communication, Problem-Solving, Project Management.

Languages: Indonesian (Native), English (Proficient).

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science - Bina Nusantara University

2022 - Present

· Current GPA: 3.81

EXPERIENCE

Scholarship Student Mentor - SASC Binus University

Mar 2024 - Present

- Provide guidance and support to mentees to increase & maintain their academic performance.
- Conducted regular mentoring sessions to track progress and address any academic challenges.
- Communicate with supervisor on mentoring progress and challenges.
- Mentee's academic GPA improved from 1.8 to 2.2.

Creative and Design Activist - HIMTI BINUS

2023 - Present

- Participated in events organized by HIMTI as video editor and mentor.
- Mainly handling video editing task and instagram feeds.
- Communicating with others on the concept of the content.

Mentor - HIMTI Leadership Training 2024

Mar 2024

- Guiding aspiring activist on finishing their task in Design and Documentation Division.
- Review and provide constructive feedback on design projects and assignments.

Co-Coordinator of Design and Documentation Division - TECHNO 2023 Apr 2023 - Oct 2023

- As Co-Coordinator, I mainly manage divison tasks, and communicate with division members, coordinator, and other division members.
- Work on video editing task, including creating promotional videos and after-movie content for the welcoming party event.

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

- Belajar Data Science Dicoding 2024
- Introduction to Machine Learning US Great Learning 2024
- · What is Generative AI? LinkedIn Learn 2024
- Introduction to Generative AI Google Cloud 2023